<resources>
    <string name="app_name">City Guide</string>
    <string name="mumbai">Mumbai is located in the state of Maharashtra. It is famously known as the capital of Maharashtra and the financial capital of India. Earlier it was known as Bombay. Its name is derived from the name of the goddess Mumba (a form of Parvati) who is the goddess of fishermen. It has wide localities of fishermen because it lies near the western coast which is a good source of fish. It borders the Arabian Sea. It is one of the most populous cities in the world and also a dream city for many people in India. The famous Reserve Bank of India, Gateway of India and Elephanta Caves are located here. The famous Dabbawala army also resides in Mumbai. The city contributes a big share of the national economy of India.
It’s my favourite city for various reasons. The countrywide famous Juhu beach and marine drive are very relaxing places to visit. People can visit these places for evening walks and during the monsoon season to enjoy themselves. The monsoon in the city is the best time to be here.We also have film city which gives a sneak peek into the glamorous life of Bollywood. We can stroll around on the streets and enjoy pocket-friendly street food and buy branded clothes at lower rates in the markets around the city. It’s famous street foods like vada pav and pav bhaji are not only pocket friendly but utterly delicious as well.
The grand celebration of Ganesh Chathurthi and many other festivals is also a striking attraction of the city. It also has an active nightlife as the city remains awake 24×7. It is difficult to survive in Mumbai unless you work very hard to sustain yourself in a fast-moving city. Therefore, when people work hard they party harder after work. This is the reason why the city is awake 24×7.
The travel in the local trains of the city is altogether a very different experience. More than everything else the people make a place. The people of Mumbai are very helpful and accepting. They celebrate all festivities together irrespective of any differences. The people are honest and punctual.</string>
    <string name="chennai">Chennai is considered to be one of the biggest cities throughout the south side of the country. It is termed as the capital of Tamil Nadu. The city is widely popular for its historical background. It has been established first by the Raja of Chandragiri.

There were several forts and monuments built during the rulership of the British government. This province, back in the days, was referred to as the Madrasapattinam. In the same period, a movie was created that appealed a vast number of audiences across the globe. The film demonstrates the lifestyle of the Tamils and the rulership of the British.

In Chennai, you can see a combination of several communities across the country. This city welcomes people with any race, caste or religion with utmost warmth and politeness. Thus, visiting Chennai can be a pleasant experience for you.</string>
    <string name="delhi">Delhi city is filled with several rare museums, temples, monuments, tombs, forts, mausoleums, fortress, and so on. This city has been ruled and owned by various empires, invaders, and kingdoms in the ancient period.

Besides, most of the widely popular movements of India took place in Delhi. It also has been termed as the capital by the ancient Mughal emperors and the Hindu Kingdom.

Delhi is considered to be highly famous across the state and also amongst foreign visitors. Due to its incredibly vast culture and interesting historical background. This city has also been destroyed and built again for around seven times.

It has been termed as the capital since ancient times or for over a thousand years. Besides, it was also termed as the capital of the state during the rule of the Muslim Kings. For instance, the Delhi of the current time was established by Shah Jahan. The palace of the city was the red fort back then.

The ancient Delhi was present close to the Chandni Chowk and the Red Fort. Back in the ancient time, there used to be a beautiful lake situated near the Chandni Chowk.

While Delhi was under the rule of Altumash, and Qutubudin-Aibak, it was located nearer to the Mehrauli and Qutub Minar.

Whereas, during the rule of Lodi dynasty, the locations closer to the Lodi gardens and the tombs became their official headquarters. Similarly, every Muslim king decided to take up the locations for themselves according to their needs or choices.

I</string>
    <string name="kolkata">Kolkata is considered to be the second biggest city in India. This city is famous for its beauty and on-going development. The metropolis situated in the town is around 350 years old. It is known to the capital of West Bengal.Everything in this city is famous for its several popular monuments, cuisines, places, and so on. The streets of Kolkata are typically filled with innovation and life amongst the chaos, vividity, and so on. This city is a mixture of both modern and traditional cultures.

There are numerous systems for transportation available in this city. The trams are also available in Kolkata since the ancient times. The provision of the underground metro services took place first in Kolkata.

Besides, this city is widely famous shopping location. It is highly visited by individuals from various parts of the state to purchase several things and products at a wholesale rate.

Kolkata is known widely for its splendid celebration of Durga Puja. The city gets filled with the large crowd during the occasion of Durga Puja. The gathering takes place for the celebration of this festival. Therefore, it is stated to be a pleasant time to visit Kolkata. During this occasion, the entire city is decorated with millions of sparkly and vibrant lights</string>
    <string name="tuticorin">Tuticorin is considered to be the second biggest city in India. This city is famous for its beauty and on-going development. The metropolis situated in the town is around 350 years old. It is known to the capital of West Bengal.Everything in this city is famous for its several popular monuments, cuisines, places, and so on. The streets of Kolkata are typically filled with innovation and life amongst the chaos, vividity, and so on. This city is a mixture of both modern and traditional cultures.

There are numerous systems for transportation available in this city. The trams are also available in Kolkata since the ancient times. The provision of the underground metro services took place first in Kolkata.

Besides, this city is widely famous shopping location. It is highly visited by individuals from various parts of the state to purchase several things and products at a wholesale rate.

Kolkata is known widely for its splendid celebration of Durga Puja. The city gets filled with the large crowd during the occasion of Durga Puja. The gathering takes place for the celebration of this festival. Therefore, it is stated to be a pleasant time to visit Kolkata. During this occasion, the entire city is decorated with millions of sparkly and vibrant lights</string>
    <string name="tirunelveli">Tirunelveli is considered to be the second biggest city in India. This city is famous for its beauty and on-going development. The metropolis situated in the town is around 350 years old. It is known to the capital of West Bengal.Everything in this city is famous for its several popular monuments, cuisines, places, and so on. The streets of Kolkata are typically filled with innovation and life amongst the chaos, vividity, and so on. This city is a mixture of both modern and traditional cultures.

There are numerous systems for transportation available in this city. The trams are also available in Kolkata since the ancient times. The provision of the underground metro services took place first in Kolkata.

Besides, this city is widely famous shopping location. It is highly visited by individuals from various parts of the state to purchase several things and products at a wholesale rate.

Kolkata is known widely for its splendid celebration of Durga Puja. The city gets filled with the large crowd during the occasion of Durga Puja. The gathering takes place for the celebration of this festival. Therefore, it is stated to be a pleasant time to visit Kolkata. During this occasion, the entire city is decorated with millions of sparkly and vibrant lights</string>
    <string name="madurai">Madurai is considered to be the second biggest city in India. This city is famous for its beauty and on-going development. The metropolis situated in the town is around 350 years old. It is known to the capital of West Bengal.Everything in this city is famous for its several popular monuments, cuisines, places, and so on. The streets of Kolkata are typically filled with innovation and life amongst the chaos, vividity, and so on. This city is a mixture of both modern and traditional cultures.

There are numerous systems for transportation available in this city. The trams are also available in Kolkata since the ancient times. The provision of the underground metro services took place first in Kolkata.

Besides, this city is widely famous shopping location. It is highly visited by individuals from various parts of the state to purchase several things and products at a wholesale rate.

Kolkata is known widely for its splendid celebration of Durga Puja. The city gets filled with the large crowd during the occasion of Durga Puja. The gathering takes place for the celebration of this festival. Therefore, it is stated to be a pleasant time to visit Kolkata. During this occasion, the entire city is decorated with millions of sparkly and vibrant lights</string>
    <string name="goa">Goa is considered to be the second biggest city in India. This city is famous for its beauty and on-going development. The metropolis situated in the town is around 350 years old. It is known to the capital of West Bengal.Everything in this city is famous for its several popular monuments, cuisines, places, and so on. The streets of Kolkata are typically filled with innovation and life amongst the chaos, vividity, and so on. This city is a mixture of both modern and traditional cultures.

There are numerous systems for transportation available in this city. The trams are also available in Kolkata since the ancient times. The provision of the underground metro services took place first in Kolkata.

Besides, this city is widely famous shopping location. It is highly visited by individuals from various parts of the state to purchase several things and products at a wholesale rate.

Kolkata is known widely for its splendid celebration of Durga Puja. The city gets filled with the large crowd during the occasion of Durga Puja. The gathering takes place for the celebration of this festival. Therefore, it is stated to be a pleasant time to visit Kolkata. During this occasion, the entire city is decorated with millions of sparkly and vibrant lights</string>


</resources>